#### **EVAN WONG**



### **Contacting Evan**

You may contact me at e.van.wong1983@gmail.com or my mobile number +60126231527

# **Summary**

I graduated from OUM (Post Graduate Diploma in ERP (SAP), majoring in FI and MM) with exemption to get MBA in Singapore (7 Months), SAP Certification in FICO exemption after this course without attending classes. I had obtained Grade A in FI module with a 1 year hands on experience implementing 3 company code for a group.

Testimonial with previous employer with attitude and work endorsement.

I am a visionary, goal oriented candidate, a leader, tends to give more values to existing company than I can as an individual, ambitious, talented and creative with dedicated individual, a fast learner and problem solver, positive attitude, outgoing and able to take extremely hard challenges, optimistic. I am energetic, self motivated, adaptable, commited and responsible person. I have excellent interpersonal and communication skills. I work well as a team player as well as independently. I can guide and lead the way to project success with great solution and idea.

#### **ATTENDED**

Accounts in form 4 and 5, grade B4 on results Taken FI module with Grade A Fundamental knowledge on accounting AP, AR, BM, GL, P&L and Balance Sheet

### Specialties:

Work effectively in a team environment, providing knowledge transfer as needed. Dedicated team player and leader with good communication and written skills. A positive thinker and team player and leader, trustworthy, mature, self-motivated and independent with strong sense of responsibility and initiative

## **Experience**

## **Technology Consultant**

### **Alphamatic Systems Sdn Bhd**

January 2013 – December 2013 (1 year)

Pre Sales for Technology Below, Meeting with customer, Drafting proposal and Presentation to existing and new customer, Analyze customer environment and document requirements, propose solution.

Provide proposal and study existing environment with upgrade of solution for the organization

Provide POC for technology products

Provide unit test on technology implemented

### **Technology Specialist**

### **Alphamatic Systems Sdn Bhd**

July 2011 – December 2013 (2 years 6 months) Puchong

Lead Engineer and Third Level Support before Principal. Managed to solve principal escalation problem. Symantec Backup Exec and Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011. Presales presentation to customer on Exchange 2010, Trend Micro Deep Security (DS) and Deep Security Appliance (TDA), Vmware 5.1, Physical to Virtual Conversion, Vmware SRM, Backupexec, Storagescraft basically enteprise technology solution. Provide unit test on technology implemented

Detect problem and root causes, solve incident and problem with system and technology before escalation to principal for design issues.

Implement enhancement and performance on implemented technology and solution.

**Experience Gained:** 

Planning, Coordinating with Customer, Sales and Company Manpower.

Leading technology implementation and functions

Virtualization

Achievements:

Trend Micro Certified Security Expert (TCSE)

MCITP Exchange Admin

Vmware Certified Professional (VCP)

### **Projects:**

Migration of Exchange(Nilai University), Mcafee Orchestrator Implementation (SBM), Vmwre SRM (SBM), Exchange Upgrade & Ms CRM 2011(Alphamatic), Migration of Active Directory (RPCM), Virus Remediation (GLOMAC), Upgrade SEPM version (JCMS Rewards), Upgrade ESXi version (Yee Lee), Configuring Netapp, Migration Esxi (Bluescope) & etc

## Working Timeline Implementation:

Setup on technology stacks such as Microsoft AD, Dynamics CRM 2011, Exchange, Vmware Esxi, Trend Micro Antivirus Software, Symantec Endpoint Protection Software, Troubleshooting and support for technology stacks Microsoft AD, Dynamics CRM 2011,

Exchange, Vmware Esxi, Trend Micro Antivirus Software, Symantec Endpoint Protection Software, Mcafee Orchestrator Software

Provides training to customer on technology implementation for maintenance and support on existing implemented technology

### **Senior System Engineer**

### **Enable DotCom Sdn Bhd**

April 2010 – June 2011 (1 year 3 months)Kota Damansara

Experience Gained:

Server Environment Technology

**Enteprise Solution Product** 

Achievements:

Symantec Backup Exec 2010 Config and Admin

Projects:

Standby on Weekly Maintenance

Standby on Suruhanjaya Tenaga (ST)

Troubleshoot end user problem printer, network, firewall, OS, application and system error Implement and troubleshoot Microsoft Exchange 2003 and 2007 certificate, Implement and troubleshoot Microsoft technologies, Implement and troubleshoot backup software such as CA Arc Serve, Symantec Backup Exec Windows Server 12.5 and 2010 Configure and implement HP storageworks and IBM storage which using HP Management Tools,

Insight manager and IBM storage software,

Implement, troubleshoot and manage Symantec Endpoint Protection Manager,

Implement, troubleshoot and manage Trend Micro server console,

Implement MS SQL Server 2005 and 2008,

Install, Implement, Troubleshoot Windows Server 2003 and 2008 with R2,

Implement M86 Mailmarshal and Webmarshal,

Finetuning performance of servers and users machine.

Implement and configuring DNS, DHCP server, Microsoft Virtual PC, Server and VMware Server, Vmware Player,

Implement and configuring router, switches and WLAN

Support: Handle customer site which is in Suruhanjaya Tenaga which consists of Cisco core switches, Cisco WLAN controller, Access Point, Nmetrics Application Monitor, Orion Solarwind Network Performance Monitor, Astaro Firewall, Mailmarshal, Webmarshal and McAfee IPS Intrusion Prevention System.

# **Support Engineer**

### Forte Tech Solutions Sdn. Bhd., UEM Group Berhad

2008 – June 2010 (2 years) Cyberjaya

Experience Gained:

Push email system Notifylink

Remote access RSUP software

Trend Micro Antivirus Server Setup

Patch Management, Active Directory

R & D Cycle

Developer, Engineer, Support and Trainer Experties

Achievements:

MCITP Server Admin

### Projects:

Sun Outlook Connector (Sun System Email Server connection to Outlook)

Notifylink (Push Emails to Blackberry)

Trend Micro Officescan Server

Build push email server notifylink, setup for all directors, support all directors on blackberry (UEM Group of Companies),

Handling tickets on blackberry support, pc and laptop supports on troubleshooting,

Building and maintaining the push email server notifylink,

Research on product notifylink, remote support- rsup, Outlook using Sun Microsystem as backend, asset management, virtualization server and Sun Convergence,

Building and configuring Trend Micro antivirus server,

Maintaining Active Directory, users access, updating user info and permission for folders and domain login,

Research and test new devices and application of new technology,

Prepare documentation for all research and projects taken.

Make and prepare presentation for users/employees on new product launch,

Provide support to existing customer in pharmaniaga berhad,

Hands-on on server backup, implementation, exchange migration and server clean up with virtualization using Vmware Technology,

Patching on existing notifylink server, active directory server and file server on Microsoft Security patching downloads, and notifylink version upgrades

## **Call Center Representative**

### **IBM**

July 2007 – 2008 (1 year) Cyberjaya

Experience Gained: Call Centre Environment Customer Urgency on Issue Problem Solving Technique

Achievements:

Call Centre Agent Awards of the Month

Level 2 Supporting Singapore Desktop and Laptop users

To help customer troubleshooting windows problem to verify hardware problem if it is faulty proceed with exchange

Learn Skill as in keying in problem and creating a report based on customer issue and solve it on the phone, verify hardware health and proceed with change if still under warranty.

# Languages

### 1. English

Full professional proficiency

### 2. Malay

Professional working proficiency

# 3. Chinese

Elementary proficiency

# **Certifications**

# **MCITP Server Admin**



**Microsoft** 

April 2011 – 2014

# **MCITP Exchange Admin**



**Microsoft** 

April 2013 – 2016

# **Trend Micro Certified Security Expert (TCSE)**



**Trend Micro** 

October 2011 – 2013

# **Vmware Certified Professional (VCP)**



**VMware** 

October 2013 - 2016

# **Skills & Expertise**

- Technical Support
- Troubleshooting
- Project Planning
- Pre-Sales Technical..
- Solution Implementation

- Technical Consultation
- Problem Solving
- Customer Support
- ICT Consultancy
- SAP FICO

#### Evan also knows about...

- SAP MM
- SAP R/3
- SAP ERP

### **Education**

### **Lithan Education @ Open University Malaysia**

Post Graduate Diploma in Enterprise Resource Planning, ERP (SAP), 3.56

2012 - 2013

I have learn how SAP works in FI and MM modules, a thorough phases for ERP implementation and open to the new world of SAP. This enable progression to further study and research; develop and practice skills in SAP; and develop problem solving skills which will enable me to demonstrate skills in the implementation and maintenance of ERPs as well as recognizing the overall business context in which such systems are to be found.

# Asia Pacific University College of Technology and Innovation

Higher Diploma, Business Information Technology, Credit

2001 - 2003

### **Additional**

#### 1. Interests

- o Snooker,
- o Console Games (PS3 and PS4),
- o Badminton,
- o Running,
- o Swimming,
- o Reading Books.

# 2. Personal Detail

**Birthday** February 11, 1983 **Marital Status** Married